<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Notes - Jon Heslop]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Notes - Jon Heslop]]></description>
        <link>https://jonheslop.com</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 10:22:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://jonheslop.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Week 43]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[* On Monday I went to see [And So I Watch You From Afar](https://www.asiwyfa.com) play through their debut album it was huge and properly good. Every track is a banger.
* After that I basically had a cold the rest of week which is not worth talking about.
* The vid of AOC grilling Zuckerberg is brilliant. He and Facebook have so much to answer for.
* Adjacently related [this LRB piece on America](https://www.lrb.co.uk/v41/n18/eliot-weinberger/one-summer-in-america) was really depressing (and long) but I couldn’t help reading it all.
* On Friday I saw [Battles](https://www.bttls.com/) which was bangin’. I haven’t seen anyone play drums like he does. Although they were having some sort of technical issues with a synth or something, I couldn’t hear anything wrong but it seemed to be stressing them out. I often wonder what that must feel like, artists having a bad time on stage whilst the crowd is loving it anyway… tricky.
* Bec and I peeled 8kgs of onions and jarred them in vinegar, this is becoming a proper Christmas tradition now.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/43-week-notes</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/43-week-notes</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Week 42]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[* Olga Tokarczuk won the Nobel prize for literature and a while back I started *Flights* but I never finished and now feel like I should try harder.
* I did however read the first two parts of Phillip Pullman’s new Book of Dust trilogy which I thoroughly enjoyed.
* I made my first non-government open source [contributions](https://github.com/denoland/deno/pull/3140) to [Deno](https://deno.land) which was exciting. They were only cop out CSS edits though, need to get brave and write some TypeScript.
* A couple of weeks ago I levelled up my nerd creds and got a myself a very small [mechanical keyboard](https://olkb.com/planck) it’s fun, but I am still slow at typing.
* MCD’s newsletter [Electric Eel](https://www.mcdbooks.com/electric_eel/) continues to be great. [This weeks](https://www.mcdbooks.com/electric_eel/the-deity-of-deceit) was particularly interesting which introduced me to [Meduza](https://meduza.io/en), an English language independent Russian news outlet.
* Really enjoyed this episode of [Politics Theory Other](https://www.patreon.com/poltheoryother) about [land ownership and the affordable housing shortage](https://soundcloud.com/poltheoryother/62-land-for-the-many-w-beth-stratford)
* I had dinner last night at Roti King, a Malaysian restaurant, big queue but it was delicious.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/42-week-notes</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/42-week-notes</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Week 47]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[* If you haven’t [registered to vote](https://www.gov.uk/register-to-vote) you have a few more days to do it, it takes less than 5 minutes
* It was my last day at GDS on Thursday, it’s been a long time coming but it suddenly happened all of a sudden and took me back a bit.
* Had a great evening at the pub with people though, thanks to everyone who came
* I was bought a [very nice book](https://www.workman.com/products/the-noma-guide-to-fermentation) I didn’t know existed by the [Noma](https://noma.dk/) people about fermatation. Very much looking forward to stinking out our kitchen
* [Sasha Baron Cohen gave a speech](https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/nov/22/sacha-baron-cohen-facebook-propaganda) this week at the Anti-Defamation League was pretty great and worth reading
* It reminded me about this [excellent mini essay](https://platforms.fyi/) by [Robin Sloan](https://www.robinsloan.com/) which very eloquently summises what is wrong with Twitter and Facebook and how some sort of negative feedback loop would benefit everyone.
* I’ve been enjoying [these daily drops](https://soundcloud.com/search?q=novara%20burner) of election coverage from [James Butler](https://twitter.com/piercepenniless/)
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/47-week-notes</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/47-week-notes</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sign me up to the week notes brigade]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As uncomfortable as it makes me feel, I am going to try and give this week notes thing a try. I’d like to get better at communicating what I do and I think the discipline will be good for me. Hopefully it’ll serve as some sort of coherent record of what I have been doing.

So this is it, a static site powered by [Eleventy]. It’s based on the [Eleventy base blog] but styled with [Tachyons]. It rebuilds and deploys automatically when changes are pushed to [Github], using [Now] by [Zeit], which makes it effortless.

[eleventy]: https://www.11ty.io

[eleventy base blog]: https://github.com/11ty/eleventy-base-blog

[tachyons]: http://tachyons.io/

[github]: https://github.com/jonheslop/week-notes

[now]: https://zeit.co/now

[zeit]: https://zeit.co/
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/7-week-notes-brigade</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/7-week-notes-brigade</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stubbing the Payment Request API for testing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Earlier this year I worked on making [Apple Pay] and [Google Pay] available to users of [GOV.UK Pay]. Which [we blogged when we launched](https://technology.blog.gov.uk/2019/05/30/how-we-implemented-apple-pay-and-google-pay-on-gov-uk-pay/).

Initially I intended to make it all work with the [Payment Request API], which is the open standard but after reading the docs and having a meeting with Apple, I decided the benefits of using Apple’s extra methods and helps made using the [Apple Pay JS API] a no brainer. It doesn’t require you to include any extra script tags as it’s all built into Safari. Apple has [since made Safari more compaitble](https://developer.apple.com/documentation/safari_release_notes/safari_12_1_release_notes#3130317) with the [Payment Request API] so I might revisit going vanilla once users have had chance to update to the latest version.

On the other hand I had a go with the Google Pay JS API which shims itself to work in every browser and drops about twelve different tracking scripts into your page to see what you might be buying. So I went with the a [standard Payment Request API](https://developers.google.com/pay/api/web/guides/paymentrequest/tutorial) approach, declaring Google Pay as the payment provider.

## Testing

Next came to work out how we could write browser tests for this, we use [Cypress] which is excellent. However I’d need to stub Apple Pay and the Payment Request API. This turned out to be fairly straight forward I didn’t find much whilst searching for solutions save for this out of date [repo by IndieGoGo].

Cypress makes it pretty easy to stub out a browser function by using the `onBeforeLoad` hook.

```js
cy.visit(`/pay`, {
  onBeforeLoad: (win) => {
    // Stub Apple Pay API (which only exists within Safari)
    win.ApplePaySession = getMockApplePayClass(
      validPaymentRequestResponse,
      "valid@email.test"
    );
  },
});
```

## Stub for Apple Pay

Apple has quite a few functions that need to be stubbed in order to simulate what happens for real.

```js
// Mock class for Apple Pay
const getMockApplePayClass = (validPaymentRequestResponse, email) => {
  class MockApplePaySession {
    completePayment() {
      return true;
    }

    completeMerchantValidation() {
      return true;
    }

    begin() {
      if (this._onvalidatemerchant) {
        this._onvalidatemerchant({ validationURL: "https://fakeapple.url" });
      }

      if (this._onpaymentauthorized) {
        this._onpaymentauthorized({
          payment: validPaymentRequestResponse(email),
        });
      }
    }

    set onvalidatemerchant(value) {
      this._onvalidatemerchant = value;
    }

    set onpaymentauthorized(value) {
      this._onpaymentauthorized = value;
    }
  }

  // Mock function to trick JS into thinking Apple Pay is available
  MockApplePaySession.canMakePayments = () => true;
  MockApplePaySession.supportsVersion = () => true;

  return MockApplePaySession;
};
```

The `validPaymentRequestResponse` is what Apple Pay returns when the user authorises using their device. You can see [an example reponse here](https://github.com/alphagov/pay-frontend/blob/ad6ece196ced3822ef26547edebcd05f306bb85e/test/cypress/integration/web-payments/apple-pay.spec.js#L8-L36).

## Stub for Payment Request API

We don’t need to stub anything Google specific here the implementation is just the vanilla [Payment Request API].

The shim to add the API to Cypress is a little different from above and for some reason I needed to do it two different ways for headed and headless.

```js
cy.visit(`/pay`, {
  onBeforeLoad: win => {
    // Stub Payment Request API
    if (win.PaymentRequest) {
      // If we’re running in headed mode
      cy.stub(win, 'PaymentRequest', getMockPaymentRequest(validPaymentRequestResponse))
    } else {
      // else headless
      win.PaymentRequest = getMockPaymentRequest(validPaymentRequestResponse)
    }
  }
```

And then the mock payment request is much simpler.

```js
const const getMockPaymentRequest = validPaymentRequestResponse => {
  return () => {
    return {
      canMakePayment: () => new Promise(resolve => resolve(true)),
      show: () => new Promise(resolve => resolve(validPaymentRequestResponse))
    }
  }
}
```

The `validPaymentRequestResponse` when using the Payment Request API is a little different to with Apple Pay but you can [an example reponse here](https://github.com/alphagov/pay-frontend/blob/ad6ece196ced3822ef26547edebcd05f306bb85e/test/cypress/integration/web-payments/google-pay.spec.js#L8-L28).

Anyway hopefully that will be useful for anyone looking to do this.

[apple pay]: https://applepaydemo.apple.com/

[google pay]: https://pay.google.com/about/

[gov.uk pay]: https://www.payments.service.gov.uk/

[payment request api]: https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Payment_Request_API/Using_the_Payment_Request_API

[apple pay js api]: https://developer.apple.com/documentation/apple_pay_on_the_web/apple_pay_js_api

[cypress]: https://www.cypress.io/

[repo by indiegogo]: https://github.com/indiegogo/apple-pay-js-stubs
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/10-stubbing-apple-and-google-pay</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/10-stubbing-apple-and-google-pay</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Found links]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[# [Using CSS Grid the right way](https://vgpena.github.io/using-css-grid-the-right-way/)

I’ve used CSS Grid a few times now but I still sorta struggle with the mental model and end up trying things out in a tedious fashion, Violet’s write up featured loads of useful tips that really helped me get my head around using it IRL.

# [Font Review Journal](http://fontreviewjournal.com/)

What a treasure trove of in depth write ups about fonts! I really enjoyed reading a few of these this week, particularly [Galaxie Copernicus](http://fontreviewjournal.com/galaxie-copernicus/) and [Windsor](http://fontreviewjournal.com/windsor/).

# [Future Fonts](https://www.futurefonts.xyz/)

Future Fonts sells experimental <abbr title="work in progess">WIP</abbr> fonts. What a great idea‽

# [Monetising data](https://twitter.com/AlbyEarley/status/1098530189422874629)

I’ve been a fan of CityMapper (their iOS release notes are proper good) but the annoucement of an Oyster card rival that will undercut the price sounds like a (morally) questionable business model. [This Twitter thread](https://twitter.com/AlbyEarley/status/1098530189422874629) does a great job explaning why.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/8-found-links</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/8-found-links</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How I protect my privacy online]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[For past year or so I’ve been actively trying to protect my online privacy by making decisions about what products I use, it started with switching to [Firefox] and ended up in leaving Instagram.

[Surveillance capitalism] is scary and I want to minimise my exposure to it. A couple of weeks back Maciej Cegłowski wrote [this brilliant essay](https://idlewords.com/2019/06/the_new_wilderness.htm) how we need to transform how we think about privacy by comparing it to how 100 years ago no one was interesting in protecting the environment.

*Here’s a little list of the things I’ve done:*

## I use Firefox with strict browser privacy enabled

[Firefox] repects it’s user privacy and has lots of features that actively help. For example [Firefox] blocks adverts and tracking pixels. [Safari] is not bad either.

## I switched from Gmail to ProtonMail

[Proton] is probably overkill [Fastmail] would is good too. As with most of these things, if you’re not paying, you are the product.

## I deleted my Facebook account

I like to think most people know why Facebook is bad, but just in case here are five articles: [1], [2], [3], [4] and [5].

## I don’t use Instagram anymore

This was probably the hardest habit for me to shake but last summer I bit the bullet and deleted the app. I probably miss out on some excellent stories but I like to think it’s good for my mental health.

## I use DuckDuckGo instead of Google for search

[DuckDuckGo] doesn’t track you like Google does. There are some searches that [DuckDuckGo] is not so good at. For instance pub opening times. But in those cases you can add `g!` to the end of you search and it redirects to Google. They have a good explainer on [why you should care about tracking](https://donttrack.us/).

## Firefox containers

[Firefox containers] are really useful for keeping trackers in check. I have a container which is signed into my Youtube account, and when I launch a youtube url it opens in this container keeping the rest of my browsing separate and disconnected. I could use Youtube without an account but the fact is subscriptions are the best way to find the videos you want rather than the trending stuff the algorithm recommends.

## Twitter via TweetBot

I use [TweetBot], I don’t use Twitter.com or the Twitter iOS app this means tweets are in chronological order, I see no promoted tweets nor do I have to put up with Twitter suggesting who I follow or what is trending.

## DNS with 1.1.1.1

When you ask you computer to access a website the first thing that happens is a DNS lookup to find out where that web address lives. Usually you ISP does this lookup for you, they [log this and use it for advertising](https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2018/04/how-to-keep-your-isps-nose-out-of-your-browser-history-with-encrypted-dns/). Using [1.1.1.1] which is run by [Cloudflare] is private and also way faster.

## DNS over HTTPS within Firefox

This is new and also very similar to the above, Firefox are the only browser that support it and this wound the ISPs up so much they [awarded Firefox *’Villan of the Year’*](https://techcrunch.com/2019/07/05/isp-group-mozilla-internet-villain-dns-privacy/), silly.

## 1Password

This is less about privacy more about security, but I used to have a well flimsy password method, now I rely on [1Password] to generate and store my passwords for me. I only have to remember one password (see what they did there). Make sure it’s something good, mine is a 28+ character phrase.

[surveillance capitalism]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Surveillance_capitalism

[firefox]: https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/new/

[safari]: https://www.apple.com/safari/

[fastmail]: https://www.fastmail.com/

[1.1.1.1]: https://1.1.1.1

[firefox containers]: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/containers

[tweetbot]: https://tapbots.com/tweetbot/

[1password]: https://1password.com/

[duckduckgo]: https://duckduckgo.com/about

[Proton]: https://proton.me/

[cloudflare]: https://www.cloudflare.com/

[1]: https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/facebook-graph-search-war-crimes

[2]: https://theoutline.com/post/7377/facebook-is-trying-to-make-the-word-private-meaningless

[3]: https://www.wired.com/story/facebook-mark-zuckerberg-15-months-of-fresh-hell/

[4]: https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/20/shoshana-zuboff-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-google-facebook

[5]: https://theintercept.com/2019/03/06/facebook-mark-zuckerberg-privacy/
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/29-how-i-protect-my-privacy-online</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/29-how-i-protect-my-privacy-online</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Fifth Risk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[I finished reading *The Fifth Risk* by Michael Lewis today, even as a person who already believes in the value and importance of state run services, it really did highlight the incredible work that goes on that we don’t hear about (unless is goes wrong).

Government funds research and development that the market would never consider and yet down the line they reap the benefit. It also hits you with regular pangs of despair about how the Trump admin­istration is handling things such as climate change.

The final section is a little Hollywood but overall it’s a fun, easy read.

The [Guardian published a version](https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/sep/27/this-guy-doesnt-know-anything-the-inside-story-of-trumps-shambolic-transition-team) of the first chapter as part of *[The long read](https://www.theguardian.com/news/series/the-long-read)* series.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/8-the-fifth-risk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/8-the-fifth-risk</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Archive]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Before I got going on the [redesign](/posts/15-redesign), I went back and dug out my old websites and have made an (incomplete) history of them all.

* [2017] - this one has things in common with this one
* [2012] - this was a good one, I made this when I was freelancing before I moved back to London
* [2011] - I liked this one too, this was a basically a carbon copy of [Naz Hamid’s](https://nazhamid.com/) ‘The personal page‘ idea, it was a great idea.
* [2010] - This one was well ugly
* [2009] - This was the first one I made after getting a job I think

I have had a website as far back as maybe 2001 but I think they might be lost forever, which is a real shame because they would be well funny now.

[2017]: https://2017.jonheslop.com/

[2012]: https://2012.jonheslop.com/

[2011]: https://2011.jonheslop.com/

[2010]: https://2010.jonheslop.com/

[2009]: https://2009.jonheslop.com/
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/15-archive</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/15-archive</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ffondo 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Gran Ffondo number three at Fforest. Weather was brill, company incredible. Jackson and the Fforest crew smashed it as usual. And Maude has the time of her life running around like a nutter for four days.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/ffondo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/ffondo</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 11:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Holthausen]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Ulf’s from a village in Germany, he’d always mentioned that I should visit sometimes. At Easter around
there they always have big fires, where they stack 'old christmas trees' in a huge stack and burn them.
Different villages stack them differently.

It sounded fun! I suggested we ride there. So after a few years of not being organised enough, Ulf planned
it all out.

We left London at 3pm on a Wednesday and arrived at 6pm on the Friday.

London - 120km - Harwich

\~ Ferry ~

Hoek Van Holland - 240km - Erle

\~ Sleep ~

Erle - 160km - Holthausen
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/holthausen</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/holthausen</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 19:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dulwich Hamlet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Went to see Dulwich Hamlet play Tauton Town. My second ever football match (first - Arsenal vs. West Brom \[1-0]).

Was fun, I enjoyed the chants, they won 2 nil and had hopes about not getting relegated (but they did).
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/dulwich-hamlet</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/dulwich-hamlet</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 11:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gather 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Every summer we head over to Fforest for Gather and help out with the workshops and see a lot of familiar faces.

This year we went for two weeks, the first was Gather, the second we stayed on and worked remotely from the farm, it was great I think we’ll definitely make that a regular thing.

On the last few nights, the moon was just a slither and I managed to get a few nice shots of the Milky Way which was clearly visible from right outside our Crog.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/gather-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/gather-2023</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:11:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redesign]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[No one needs me to mention that 2020 was a hectic year, not least because of the pandemic. But besides that Bec and I were very privileged to find ourselves entirely distracted with the renovation of a house. Within which, we are now very much enjoying simply living in.

But I think in the come down of all that doing I found myself with excess energy from all the extra free time we suddenly that I told myself it was high time I redesigned my website.

After messing with [Next.js](https://nextjs.org/) before the 1.0 release and whilst finding elements of it great some of it was too finickity and annoying enough that I wasn‘t interested for a while. But after watching the changelogs I was curious to give it another go.

The ecosystem around it is great and it’s much faster now and it’s doesn’t burden the browser with anywhere near as much JS now.

So here it is my new website, I had been itching for an excuse to buy [Söhne](https://klim.co.nz/retail-fonts/soehne/) since it launched and have used Buch (weight) throughout.

I’ve also used [TailwindCSS](https://tailwindcss.com/) having been a longstanding user of [Tachyons](http://tachyons.io/) before that. Tailwind is really powerful and I think going forward it will be my go to.
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/15-redesign</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/15-redesign</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 20:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gaye & Nick’s]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Dropped Maude of to stay with my Aunt and Uncle whilst we went to Berlin to see my brother. I love my uncle’s garden studio!
]]></description>
            <link>https://jonheslop.com/posts/gaye-and-nicks</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jonheslop.com/posts/gaye-and-nicks</guid>
            <category><![CDATA[notes]]></category>
            <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Heslop]]></dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 11:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>